翻译：Iz      Tiogy      红豆包      小布拿拿
校对&总监：Iz
后期：斯人     时间轴：深夏桃子
更多动画  就在@欧美动漫汉化军团
《开心汉堡店》第五季第十九集
最难的莫过于引诱[等待]
除虫害公司
给你  泰迪
Here you go, Teddy.
多谢你接了我这急单
Thanks for the rush order.
我真是要忙疯了
I got a hell of a busy day ahead of me.
泰迪  既然你在这里吃
Teddy, why did you ask for a to-go bag
为什么还要打包呢
if you're gonna eat it here?
我这就走  我这就走
I'm leaving, I'm leaving.
真的吗
Are you, though?
孩子们  你能忙起来可真好  泰迪
Kids. It's good that you're so busy, Teddy.
是啊  我在镇上得到了份干砌墙的工作
Yeah, I got a dry wall job in town, plus, I've been
另外我一直在打理陡峭领的一座避暑别墅
taking care of a summer house out on Craggy Neck.
今天据说会下雨
It's supposed to rain today,
所以我得把草坪家具搬到平台下面去
so I gotta put the lawn furniture under the deck.
我为我们的问题道歉
Sorry we asked.
你好  嗨  汉德利先生
Hello? Oh, hi, Mr. Handley.
你的热水器么
Your hot water heater?
是的  我今天能过去
Yeah, I could be there today.
好吧  一会儿见
All right... I'll see you soon.
现在我又接到一份工作
And now I just took another job.
我为什么要这么做  泰迪
Why would I do that?! Teddy!
冷静点  泰迪
All right, calm down, Teddy.
-我替你去陡峭领  -什么
- Hey, I'll go out to Craggy Neck for you. - What?
-真的吗  -是的 去一个
- Really? - Yeah, I want to go to a nice place
美丽的地方搬家具感觉不赖
and drag furniture under a deck.
-带上我们  -我也可以搬一搬家具
- Take us! - I could drag some furniture.
那可真是帮了我大忙了
Well, that'd be a big help.
-好嘞  -等等  如果你们都要去
- All right! - Wait, if you're all going
什么海滨别墅  那我也应该去
to some beach house, then I should go, too.
我们可以暂时休业
We could close for a little while.
但老爸  如果客人想来用餐怎么办
But, Dad, what if people want to come to the restaurant?
是啊  那到是  我
Oh, right. That's true. I p...
开玩笑的  老爸  开玩笑的
Just kidding, Dad. Just kidding.
好了  我们到了
All right, we're here.
太好了
All right!
我们到了这么美的海边
We're on the frickin' beach.
风景太美了
That is quite a view.
我知道咱家附近也是这片海
I mean, I know it's the same ocean near our house,
-但这边的更好  -我们来到海边了诶
- but this one's better. - I mean, it's on the beach.
他们搞不好是让螃蟹给他们送报纸的
They probably have crabs bringing them the newspaper.
这才是生活
That is the life.
景观如此赏心悦目
Oh, and it's so beautifully landscaped.
看那些大卵石
Look at those boulders!
吉恩  快下来
Gene, get off the boulders.
他们可喜欢我站在上面了
They love it!
我自己  能行
I got it. On my own.
-因为我很强壮  -干得不错  老爸
- Because I'm strong. - Good job, Dad!
里面也这么漂亮
Oh, so pretty inside.
门没锁  我们应该进去吗
Oh. The door's open. Should we go inside?
-去关门吗  -我想是的
- Just to close the door? - Well, I guess so.
不然要怎么关门呢
I mean, how else are we gonna close the door?
我们进来了  我们在房间里了
We're inside. We're in the house.
这是怎么发生的
How did that happen?
你们在干嘛
What are you doing?
你们这是擅闯私宅
You're trespassing.
你们进到别人家里了
You're in somebody's home.
严格讲  我们进的是别人的避暑别墅
Well, technically it's somebody's summer home.
-这是不同的  对吗  -是的
- That's different, right? - Yeah.
完全合法
Totally legal.
我们只是要关门
We're just shutting the door.
我们这是强行入侵他人住宅了吗
Are we breaking and entering?
一家人一起闯的  所以没关系
As a family. So it's okay.
过来站我边上待一会
Come stand next to me for two seconds.
假装我们在度假
It'll feel like we're on vacation.
不  琳  我们得走了
No, Lin, we should go.
感觉真好
This is nice.
我此刻觉得自己好穷
I feel really poor right now.
是啊
Yeah.
我想我们还可以再多站会
I guess we can stand here for another two seconds.
是的  然后我们就走
Yeah. And then we'll leave.
好吧  但是我们什么都不要碰
Okay. But we're not touching anything.
-是的  -当然  -当然不能碰
- Yeah. -Sure. - Of course not.
我想我现在喜欢上船了
I think I like boats now.
这些照片上的一定就是房主了
These must be the owners.
很可爱的情侣  有些年龄差
Cute couple. Little age difference
但也没关系
but that's okay.
他们还一起旅行呢
Oh, and they travel.
一定很棒
Must be nice.
推着斜塔
Pushing up the Leaning Tower.
这对真能作
Couple of hams.
你觉得我们应该买艘船吗
Do you think we should get a boat?
再订份船舶杂志
And a subscription to a boat magazine?
看看那戒指
Look at that ring!
感觉跟迪厅里的闪光灯球差不多大
Looks like a disco ball.
美国俱乐部和夜生活文化经典代表
她手上纹的54俱乐部
She's got Studio 54 on her hand.
《豪华游轮》
我想我会买一艘船
I think I'm gonna get one.
我想我要买艘船  一艘大船
I think I'm gonna get a boat; A big boat.
等等  我们在干嘛  我们得走了
Wait, what are we doing? We-we got to go.
孩子们  我们走了
Kids, we're leaving!
孩子们  我们得走...我去
Kids, we gotta go... oh, my God.
娱乐室
Game room.
老爸  欢迎来到戏谷
Oh, hey, Dad. Welcome to Funtown.
我忘了应该买座大房子
Oh, I forgot to get a big house
这样就可以放台球桌了
so we could get a pool table.
我们真的得走了  但首先
We do have to go, but first,
我也许应该教一下你们如何打台球
I should probably teach you kids how to play pool.
我们知道怎么打
We know how to play.
就把这些球摇来摇去  听碰撞声就好了
You just roll the balls and hear them click.
目前为止我领先
So far I'm winning.
太棒了
Yes.
孩子们  我这一生中还是有几件
All right, kids, there are a couple things in life
拿手活的  打台球是其中之一
I'm really good at, and pool is one of them.
其它的是什么
What are the other things?
别提汉堡
And don't say burgers.
准备好欣赏我的雷霆一击吧
Prepare for the thunder that is my break.
蒂娜  站一边去
Tina, step to the side.
我不想让余震震到你
I don't want the shockwave to hit you.
太烂了
That was terrible.
是的  我的确是这么想
Yeah, I thought maybe it was,
但我又不太确定  所以只能哇了一声
but I wasn't sure, so I just said "Whoa."
可能是这球杆的原因
It's probably the cue.
真的  这根杆...好弯
Oh, yeah. This one is... crazy warped.
我看它挺直的
It looks straight to me.
是的  不能用这么弯的杆
Yeah, you can't use a cue stick like this.
这根杆感觉比较直
Okay. This one feels not warped.
角袋  你嘴张那么大  希望你饿了哦
Corner pocket, your mouth is open, I hope you're hungry!
真该死
Damn it!
哇  这球  这球打的好吗
Whoa... Is that... is that good?
他们喜欢滑雪
They're skiers.
这两人好爱运动
So sporty, those two.
2001年美国电影
讲述哈特一家围绕一座小木屋的钟引发的惊险故事
有点《古钟传奇》的意思
Look like Hart to Hart.
你知道是谁给的我这杯水吗
Do you know who gave me this water?
冰箱给的
The refrigerator did!
什么
What?
直接从门里递出来的
Came right out of the door!
天呐
Goodness.
你在干嘛
What are you up to?
我只是很好奇这两个人是谁
I'm just curious who these people are.
看看他们读些什么书
You know, what books they read,
喜欢听什么音乐
what kind of music they like.
明白了  你在八卦
Got it. You're snooping.
什嘛  我没有八卦
What?! I'm not snooping...
我只是在观察
I'm just noticing.
当然
Sure.
他们登山了  真棒
They climbed a mountain. Good for them.
我们要不要去那间房子观察一下呢
Should we go "Notice" around in that room?
家庭办公室
Home office.
看  他们有信件  真有意思
Look, they get mail. That's fun.
我们知道他叫什么名字了  拉里・古德温
and we got a name! Larry Goodwin.
他们怎么有这么多钟
Why do they have so many clocks?
这是需要多少时间啊
How much time do you need?
好诡异  时间都停在三点十三分
Spooky. They all stopped at 3:13.
等等  都走了
Oh, wait, they all moved.
我想我明白了
I think I figured it out.
看这个  都写这古德温
Look at this: They all say Goodwin.
拉里・古德温
Larry Goodwin!
拉里是做钟表生意的
Larry's rollin' in clock money!
原来要这样才买得起海滨别墅呢
So that's how you afford a beach house.
我们都努力错方向了
We've been going about it all wrong.
你有没有看到那抽屉自己打开了
Did you see that drawer open all by itself?
自己就打开了
It just popped open.
它自己打开了  不是吗
It did, didn't it?
是的  看
Yeah, look at that.
它就这么打开了
Just popped right open.
真奇怪
Well, that's weird.
他们的结婚照片
Their wedding picture.
等等  那女人和其它照片里的女人
Wait, that woman looks different
长得不一样
than the one in all the other pictures.
还真是
She does.
前额差好多
She had a totally different forehead.
肯定是做过了
Must've got it reduced.
老妈  这不是同一个妻子
Mom, this is a different wife.
这位一定是第一任妻子
This must be the first wife!
拉里抛弃她  换了新的妻子
And Larry traded her in
一位更漂亮的模特
for a newer, prettier model.
-那个混蛋  -真是人心难测
- That bastard! - You think you know somebody!
拉里  你怎么能这样
Larry!
完了
Oh, crap.
完了  有人来了
Oh, crap. Someone's here.
你这么说是因为我要赢了吗
Are you just saying that because I'm beating you?
快躲起来
Hide.
鲍勃  琳达
Bob? Linda?
你们在吗
You guys in here?
对啊
Yeah?
为啥
Why?
对啊  为啥
Right. Why.
对啊  你们怎么进来了
Yeah. Why are you inside the house?
对啊  泰迪  问得好
Right. Teddy. Good question.
对啊  鲍勃  你们进来干嘛
Right, Bob. What are you doing in the house?
琳达  你也说句话呗
Linda? Jump in any time.
等等  这不是天台下面啊
Wait a minute, this isn't under the deck.
鲍鲍  那你喊我们进来干嘛  小笨蛋
Bobby, why'd you make us come in here, you silly?
谢谢  琳  救场救得真好
Thanks, Lin, that was great.
对不起  泰迪  我们不该进来的
Sorry, Teddy. We shouldn't have come in.
随便逛逛是么  就像买衣服前试穿一样
Poking around, huh? Trying the house on for size?
-我懂的  你们洗澡了吗  -啥  没有
- I get it. You take a bath?  - What? No.
-那亏了  -泰迪  你来干嘛
- Your loss.  - Teddy, why are you here?
我们过来不就是为了让你不用来吗
We came all this way so you wouldn't have to.
风越来越大了
The weather's getting real stormy.
我得确认一下门窗是不是都关好了
I thought I ought to make sure the house is all sealed up.
拉里・古德温可得多谢你了
Yeah, I'm sure Larry Goodwin would appreciate it.
可能他发妻在他心中都比不过你
Much more than he appreciated his first wife,
可怜她姿色不再
who dared to age.
老爸  跟上  老妈  继续
Keep up, Dad. Right on, Mom.
我完全不了解拉里
I wouldn't know anything about Larry.
连见都没见过他
I never met him.
我来这里工作前他就死了
He died before I started working here.
-拉里死了  -拉里死啦
- Larry's dead?  - Larry's dead!
对啊  很惨的意外
Yeah. Terrible accident.
他在屋顶天台滑了一跤
He slipped on the widow's walk up on the roof
摔到下面装饰用的大卵石上了
and fell onto the decorative boulders below.
我就说怎么感觉那些石头像受过心理创伤
I thought those boulders seemed traumatized.
他的妻子海伦  像天使一样
Helen, the wife, she's a doll.
是世上最好的女人
Nicest woman in the world.
她在玫瑰园里目睹了一切  真可怜
Poor thing witnessed the fall from the rose garden.
我的...  我的天
Oh, my... oh, my God.
如果这第二任妻子不只是目睹这一幕
What if Little Miss Second Wife didn't witness the death?
还亲手制造了这悲剧呢
What if she did the death?!
-绝对有可能  -什么
- Of course!  - What?
海伦为了钟表家产谋杀亲夫
Helen killed her husband for his clock fortune!
她是黑寡妇
She's a black widow!
这是一个装修品位颇高的杀人犯家
We're in the tastefully decorated house of a killer.
-装修品位确实高 -还行
- It is tastefully decorated. - It's all right.
得啦
Come on!
海伦才不是杀人犯呢
Helen's not a murderer.
琳  这个罪名可不小啊
Whoa, Lin, That's a pretty big accusation.
谋杀本来就是重罪
Ye, well, murder's a pretty big crime.
行了  该走了
All right. Time to go.
等等  等等  老爸
Whoa, whoa, whoa, Dad.
在找到证据交给警察前
We're not leaving until we find evidence
我们不能走
we can take to the fuzz.
这案子肯定变数颇多
This is a hot cold case.
这是我们该为拉里和他的钟表家族做的
Yeah, we owe it to Larry and his clock family.
你俩是说笑的吧
You two cannot be serious.
看她那阴险狡诈的狐狸眼
Look at her shifty snake eyes.
对  如果把笑容遮住的话
Yeah, if you take away her warm smile,
这是冷血杀人犯的冷血眼神
she's got the ice-cold stare of an ice-cold murderer.
如果把鼻子遮住  她看起来就很奇怪
And if you take away her nose, she looks really weird.
对  如果遮住她的半张脸
Yeah, and if you take away half of her face,
她看上去就像...  只有半张脸
she's like... half face.
各位  拜托  这可是海伦哎
Guys, come on. This is Helen we're talking about.
拉里滑倒摔下的时候  她在玫瑰园里呢
She was in the rose garden when Larry slipped and fell.
是啊  拉里  登山爱好者
Oh, you mean Larry, the mountain climber,
登山无压力  却在自家房顶不慎滑倒
who can scale the highest peak but just slipped off his own roof?
他根本不是"不慎滑倒"
'Cause he didn't slip!
是海伦把他推下去的
Helen pushed him off the widow's walk!
她推了他
She pushed him!
-不不  不会  -你们想象力太丰富
- No, no, no, no.  - You're really stretching, guys.
泰迪  再跟我们说说拉里遭遇的所谓意外
Teddy, what else can you tell us about Larry's "Accident"?
那事挺吓人的
It was a freak thing.
他靠在栏杆上  栏杆倒了
The guy leaned against the railing and it gave way.
警察说因为栏杆已经松动
The cops said it was loose.
一定是她松动的栏杆
I bet she loosened the railing.
用啥松的  魔法吗
With what? Magic?
怎么可能有东西能从木头里把螺丝取走
What could possibly remove a nail from wood?
锤子另一边  的那个东西
The back of a hammer. The-the thingies.
泰迪  她把工具箱都放哪儿
Teddy, where does she keep her tools?
她没啥工具  她不太会用
She doesn't have any tools. She's not very handy.
-而且...  算了  -怎么了  泰迪
- Also... Eh, forget it. - What, Teddy? What?
我觉得她雇我是因为寂寞
Well, I think she might be hiring me because she's lonely.
她肯定不是杀人犯
She's definitely not a killer.
她真的是最甜美的小女人了
She's really the sweetest little thing.
也不是很小  正常身材
She's not little, she's regular-sized.
光是谈到她都让我起鸡皮疙瘩了
Just talking about her gets me all frazzled.
泰迪  你是喜欢海伦吗
Teddy, do you have a crush on Helen?
什么  不是
What? Huh? No.
她喜欢你吗
Does she have a crush on you?
她会故意在你面前掉东西
Does she drop things in front of you
好让你们都弯腰去捡吗
so you both have to bend down and pick them up?
有时我们会在天台上喝茶
Sometimes we have tea on the deck
聊上几句  感觉有好几分钟那么长
and just talk for what feels like minutes.
琳达  我们能单独谈谈吗
Linda, can we have a word in private?
-不能  -可以
- No. - Yes.
干嘛  鲍勃  我干正事呢
What, Bob? I'm onto something here.
-才没有  -是正事
- You're not. - I am.
你只是在毁了
The only thing you're doing is messing up
泰迪可能拥有的大好姻缘
a possible relationship for Teddy.
这位海伦小姐听起来和善又寂寞
This Helen lady sounds like she's nice and lonely,
泰迪可能正是和善又寂寞的人的
and Teddy is probably a good match
好伴侣
for someone nice and lonely.
或任何人的好伴侣
Or anyone.
泰迪基本上应该和任何喜欢他的人约会
Teddy should date anyone that likes him, basically.
除了可能对他下毒手的人
Anyone except someone who's gonna murder him.
或许即使那样也没关系  对泰迪来说
But maybe even that's okay. For Teddy.
喔  我突然想到了
Oh my God, I just thought of something.
泰迪  拉里是摔在了后院
Teddy, so Larry landed on the decorative boulders
那些石头上吗
in the backyard?
-没错  -看这张照片
- That's right. - Look at this photo.
注意到什么了吗
Notice anything?
这把年纪  却还能驾驭大口袋短裤吗
Even at his age, Larry could still pull off cargo shorts?
根本没有石头
There are no boulders!
正确  因为是海伦到作案现场时
Exactly! 'Cause Helen put 'em there
放过去的
when she came on to the scene.
接着她把拉里推到了石头上
And then she pushed Larry right onto 'em,
一手造成他的死亡
ensuring his death.
你们这结论下得太草率了
You guys are really jumping to conclusions here.
你是想说下得太正确吧  爸
You mean pushing to conclusions, Dad?
泰迪  要怎么上天台
Teddy, how do you get up to the widow's walk?
看来我们要重演谋杀现场了
We're gonna reenact a little murder.
外面风雨真的很大
Storm's really whipping up out there!
我听不到你说的啥
I can't hear you!
外面风雨很大
The storm's really whipping up!
琳达  你不能出去
Linda! You're not going out there.
太危险了
It's too dangerous!
没事的  没问题
It's fine, it's fine!
算了  算了  就在里面好了
Never mind, never mind. Let's do it inside.
老妈的发型好惊悚
Mom's hair looks terrible.
是啊  不忍直视
I know. I can't look at her.
但也不忍不直视
But you can't look away.
我决定就往旁边看一点点
I'm just looking kind of to the side.
好  这是我想象的情况
Okay, so here's what I think happened.
-鲍勃  你是拉里  -不
- Bob, you're Larry. - No.
-善良的  死去的拉里  -我的个天
- Sweet, dead Larry. - Ugh, God.
我是海伦
I'm Helen.
一个坏人  觊觎你的钱财
I'm a bad person, and I want your money
所以要推你下去
so onto the boulders with you!
我的老腰啊
My back.
你有必要真推吗
Did you actually have to push me?
妈  我觉得这就是真相
I think that's exactly how it happened, Mom.
不会  海伦不会杀人
Nah, nah. There's no way Helen's a killer.
说真的  我觉得我  受伤了
Seriously, I think my back is... bad.
好了  好了  小宝贝
All right, all right, you baby.
来来来  我们去沙发
Let's help you onto the couch.
老爸的发型好惊悚
Dad's hair looks horrible.
一直这么惊悚
It always looks horrible.
-乖乖躺好  -我们就不该进这房子
- There we go. - We never should have come into this house.
大家不要慌
It's all right, everybody.
可能只是电力管制
It's probably just a brownout.
我一点都  不怕
I'm not, like, too scared.
海伦  你来啦
Helen! Hey. You're here.
就是她
It's her.
她的发型好赞
Her hair looks amazing.
我们去问问她在哪家做的吧
Let's ask her where she goes.
海伦  我还以为你在纽约
So, Helen, uh, I thought you were in New York.
我想来别墅歇几天
I decided to get away for a few days to my vacation home.
你们这些人在我们的度假别墅里做什么
And who are these people in my vacation home?
对了  他们是我的朋友  是一家人
Right. These are my friends. They're a family.
贝尔彻一家  抱歉  我让他们...
They're Belchers. Sorry, you see, I asked them to...
带着你们的小屁孩滚出去
You take your dirty children and get the hell out!
-老天  -海伦  对不起  我
- Oh, God. - Helen, I'm sorry. I...
我开玩笑哒
I'm kidding!
这笑话真可笑  真可怕
What a fun, terrifying joke.
她是不是很搞笑
Isn't she a hoot?
真高兴你来了
Oh, I'm glad you're here.
我在风暴里开了几个小时
I've been driving for hours in that storm.
真惊讶高速公路没封路
Surprised the roads are open.
欢迎  我是海伦
Welcome! I'm Helen.
你好  我是鲍勃
Hi, I'm Bob.
这是我家小孩  蒂娜  吉恩和露易丝
These are my kids, Tina, Gene, and Louise.
这是我的妻子琳达
And this is my wife Linda.
很高兴见到你  海伦
Nice to meet ya, Helen.
眼神交流很多啊  小姑娘
You're making a lot of eye contact, little girl.
你长着一双美丽[杀人]的手
That's a killer handshake you've got there.
多谢  我  握得很用力
Thank you. I'm, uh... I'm really squeezing.
好了  我们要在路况变糟前
Anyways, we should get home
赶回家  快走吧  孩子们
before the roads get any worse. Come on, kids.
什么  老妈  你不是要破案吗
What?! Mom, I thought you wanted to solve the crime!
安全第一  我要保护我的宝贝们
Safety first! I have to protect my babies!
海伦  你车上有什么零食啊
Helen, what car snacks do you have?
我不能站着
Oh, I need to not stand up.
-你还好吗  -他好着呢
- Are you okay? - Nah, he's fine.
他装的  起来
He's faking it. Come on.
我没装  我老婆推我的
I'm not faking. My wife pushed me.
是啊  被一个女人推了
Yeah, pushed by a lady.
-你懂的  海伦  -露易丝
- You know how that is, Helen. - Louise.
正好  我有些止疼药
You know, I have some pain relievers from back
以前我一直吃的
when I used to take a lot of pain relievers.
你要来一点吗
Would you like some?
-好的  麻烦你  -不他不需要
- Yes, please. - No, he doesn't.
-不不不  -是的  我需要  谢谢
- No, no, no. - Uh, yes, I would. Thank you.
那好  我马上回来
Great. I'll be right back.
看到没  她人很好
See? She's nice.
你觉得她喜欢我吗
Do you think she likes me?
我没法公正地评判
I'm not really a fair judge
因为她都没回答我零食的问题
since she wasn't too helpful with the car snacks.
鲍勃  我们要离开这  她是个杀人犯
Bob, we got to get out of here! She's a killer!
琳达  我哪也去不了因为有人推了我
Linda, I can't go anywhere because someone pushed me.
老妈  我们要留下来观察
Mom, we got to stay and see this through!
这会打响我们的事业
This case could make our careers!
有90%的可能她会在接下一小时杀了我们
There is a 90% chance she kills us in the next hour!
她只是个老公从屋顶摔下来的好女人
She's a nice lady whose husband fell off a roof.
你们够了
You've got to stop.
有人有古龙水吗  吉恩
Does anyone have any cologne? Gene?
没有  我已经被禁止用古龙水了
No. I'm not allowed to wear cologne again
除非我证明自己能审慎地使用它
until I prove I can be responsible with it.
我口袋有颗止咳药
I have a cough drop in my pocket.
交出来
Give it.
我只知道那女人是谋  人鱼  美人鱼
All I know is that woman is a mur... ...maid. Mermaid!
这就是美人鱼的历史
And that's the history of mermaids.
谢谢你了  老妈
Oh, thanks, Mom!
多神奇的生物  你好  海伦
Such amazing creatures. Hey, Helen.
你好  给你
Hi. And here you go.
怎么了  手不听使唤
What happened there? Crazy arms.
好在我还多带了点
Good thing there's more where that came from.
给你
Here you go.
鲍鲍
Bobby!
你们俩真有意思
What a fun couple you are!
好久都没有过这么猛的风暴了
It's been a while since we've had a storm like this.
我把所有的窗户都锁了  什么都进不来
I locked down all the windows. Nothing's getting in.
好吧  水从那扇进来了  那扇在漏水
Okay, water's getting in that one, that one's leaking.
鲍勃  她可能想毒死你
Bob, she might be trying to poison you!
老爸  你有死前心愿吗
Yeah, Dad, do you have a death wish?
没人会在药里下毒
People don't put poison in pills.
一般下在食物饮料里
They put it in food or drinks.
你知道现在来点什么最好吗
You know what would be great right now?
热巧克力
Hot chocolate.
迷你棉花糖
Mini marshmallows!
配这个最好了  可是我家没有了
Would be nice right now, but I don't have any.
你有车啊
You have a car.
不用给我了  多谢
Oh, none for me, thanks.
抱歉  我们都不喜欢热巧克力  都不
Yeah, sorry, we don't like hot chocolate, any of us.
母亲  你不能代表我
Mother, you do not speak for me.
我都不知道我不喜欢热巧克力
I didn't know I didn't like hot chocolate.
是的你不喜欢  我帮你们喝了
Yeah, you don't. I'll take theirs.
这玩意儿我能喝下一吨
I could drink a gallon of this stuff.
舌头要烧起来了  但我喜欢
It burned the crap out of my tongue, but I love it.
泰迪要死了  他死定了
Teddy's dead. He's friggin' dead!
这些止疼药好像起作用了
Hey, these pain meds are starting to kick in.
我的背感觉  好多了
And my back is feeling a... oh, much better.
乐意帮忙  我也吃了点
Happy to help. I took a couple,
我也感觉到了
and I'm right there with ya.
-这药真不错  -那是
-Yeah. These are good. - Oh, yeah.
-我都想多吃几片  -我一直多吃几片
- I'd take more. - I always take more.
海伦  我对你丈夫的事情感到抱歉
So, Helen, sorry to hear about your late husband.
是啊  他是个好人
Oh, yes, he was a good man.
好  好  好  好  好
Good, good, good, good, good.
还有好品味  是吧
Good taste, too, huh?
是啊  他选了我
Well, he chose me.
不  我是说后面那些
Oh, no, I just meant those beautiful
装饰用的漂亮石头
decorative boulders out back.
又结实又有型
So solid and jagged.
是拉里选的吗
Did Larry pick those out?
不  是我选的
Oh, no, I picked those out.
拉里对石头的品味最差了
Larry had the tackiest taste in boulders.
那么说是你选的喽
So you picked those out.
真有趣
How interesting.
很有趣
Very interesting.
-也许吧  -我没觉得好有趣
- Yeah. I guess. - I don't think so.
拉里是个登山爱好者  是吗
So, uh, Larry was quite the mountain climber, huh?
拉里吗  不  不  爱登山的是我
Larry? No. No, I'm the climber.
是我把他拽到那些山上去的
I had to drag him to all those mountains.
拉里以前喊我"圣海伦山"
Larry used to call me "Mount St. Helen."
我也不知道什么意思
Which I don't get.
所以他不是个登山爱好者喽
Oh, so he wasn't a good mountain climber?
是啊  他逊毙了
Yeah, he wasn't good at all. Huh.
完全的笨手笨脚
Total klutz.
真是典型的拉里
That's so Larry.
你家真漂亮  海伦
You know, you have such a lovely home, Helen.
看来拉里留给了你衣食无忧的生活
Looks like Larry left you very comfortable.
没有  他几乎把一切都捐给慈善机构了
Oh, no, he left nearly everything to charity.
慈善机构
Charity.
除了这所房子
Well, everything except this house.
和纽约那所  和阿斯本的
And the place in New York. And Aspen.
-还勉强能过得下去  -那啥
- I'll get by. - Uh, you know what?
我要去拉屎  有人要同去吗
I got to poop, and would anyone like to join me?
-家庭会议  -当然了
- Family meeting.
老妈  我跟你去拉
Of course, Mother, I could poop.
来吧  各位
Come on, everyone!
鲍鲍  你不一定非要来
Bobby, you might not have to go,
但我希望你试试  亲爱的
but I want you to try, honey.
我动不了
I can't move.
我就和亨利留在这
I'm gonna stay here with Henry.
-海伦  -我叫鲍勃
- Helen. - My name is Bob.
是她放的大石头  那是罪证
Okay, so she put in the boulders. That's guilty.
罪证如山
Guilty as hell.
更有理由带你们逃离这了
All the more reason to get you kids out of here.
但拉里是运动白痴
But Larry was a klutz,
也许真是他自己从屋顶摔下来的
So maybe he did just fall off his own roof.
等等  他不是把钱都捐给慈善了吗
Wait. Didn't he leave all his money to charity?
是啊  对的
Right. True.
我们怎么知道海伦说的是事实
But how do we know Helen's telling the truth about that?
好吧  无论她想干什么
Well, whatever her deal is,
我们快离开这华丽的死亡别墅
let's get out of this beautiful death house.
回到我们不堪入目的小家
And home to our hideous life house.
好吧  要有人问起来
Fine, but if anyone asks,
就说我们破案了  我们干得很漂亮
we solved this thing, and we were brilliant.
外面雨[药劲]真的下好大
It's really coming down out there.
我说雨  应该是这么表达
The rain... it's an expression, I think.
-你懂的  -我完全懂
- You get it. - I totally get it.
知道吗  你有个绝好的家庭  还有泰迪
You know, you have a wonderful family. And Teddy.
你有个绝好的家庭和泰迪
You have a wonderful family and Teddy.
真不敢相信琳达觉得你杀了你丈夫
I can't believe Linda thinks that you killed your husband.
什么  她真这么想
What? She does?
是的
She does.
她觉得是你松了栏杆
She thinks you loosened the railing,
把他推到了大石头上
and you pushed him onto the boulders.
她太可笑了  你是好人
But she's crazy, and you're nice.
外面真是越下越大了
It's really coming down out there.
这表达我要常用
I got to use that.
真是太棒了
That's a crazy expression.
好啦  我们都拉好了
Okay, we all pooped.
鲍勃  上路吧
Bob, let's hit the road.
琳达  我有点怀疑
You know, Linda, I have a suspicion
你们不是都去拉屎了
you didn't all go poop.
什么  我们当然是了
What? Of course we did.
我闻到了什么  琳达  而且不是厕所
Something smells, Linda, and it's not the bathroom.
路已经被雨水淹没了
Road's completely flooded.
今夜没人能进出此地
No one's getting in or out of here tonight.
-什么  -看来
- What? - I guess it looks like
你们必须留在这过夜了
you'll have to stay the night here.
不  没关系的  我们可以游泳回去
No. That's all right. We can swim home.
琳达  我坚持  而且我一般都能说服别人
Linda, I insist, and I always get my way.
我很固执
I'm very... pushy.
Pushy 又有推人的意思
我睡沙发
I call couch!
你还认为海伦是凶手吗
So, do you still think Helen's a murderer?
是啊  但如果我们注定要死
Yes, I do, but if we're all gonna get killed,
我宁愿玩着电子游戏死
We may as well go out playing video games.
我认为她是清白的
Well, I think she's innocent.
不  她是个食男兽  就像游戏里的吃豆人
No, she's a man-eater, like Ms. Pac Man here.
吃豆人吃幽灵和水果好吗
Ms. Pac Man eats ghosts and fruit!
别把她扯进来
Don't bring her into this!
海伦  你要我睡你房间啊
Oh, Helen, me sleep in your room?
我睡地上  对吧
On the floor though, right?
不睡地上  和你睡床上  好吧
Not on the floor? In the bed with you? Okay.
抱抱啊  没问题
Spooning? Sure.
你来抱我吗  你...
You want to be the big spoon? You want...?
不  你要我来抱你啊
No, you want me to be the big spoon.
这我可没想到
I hadn't thought of that.
听我说  我站第一班岗
Okay, I'll take first watch.
几个小时后  换你来
In a couple hours, we'll switch.
行行  都听你的  吉恩
Yeah, yup, you got it, Gene.
我不是吉恩  我是你妻子琳达
I'm not Gene. I'm your wife Linda.
摸摸我的脸
Rub my face.
琳达
Linda.
我没看见你在那儿呢
Oh, I didn't see you there.
因为我悄悄过来的
'Cause I snuck up on you.
来  跟我散散步吧
Come, take a walk with me.
-不不  我好累  -来嘛  来
- No, no. I'm pretty tired. - Come, come.
我要拖你走啦  跟我来
I'm grabbing your arm, you're walking with me.
这就对了
Here we go.
你干嘛想到这上面来
Why you want to come up here?
我想跟你谈谈来着
I wanted to check in with you.
你想跟我谈
You wanted to check in, huh,
-在天台上么  -是的
- on the widow's walk? - I did.
你老公说你认为我杀了我老公
Because your husband says you think I killed my husband.
没没  别听他胡说
No, no, don't listen to him.
他  他早茫了
He's-he's stoned out of his mind.
你就是这么想的  我从你脸上看得出来
You think I did it. I can tell by your face.
而且我每靠近你一步
And because you're backing away.
你就退后一步
Every time I walk towards you.
-在这天台上  -海伦
- On the widow's walk. - Helen.
-我老公就在这儿死的  -死了  拉里
- Where my husband died. - Died, Larry.
看看谁来啦
Look who's here!
桌球小子
The pool man!
摆起来  吉恩
Rack 'em up, Gene.
该我上场了
Pool's in session.
好耶  逗比老爸来啦
Yay! It's loopy Dad!
我说话很奇怪吗
Am I talking funny?
得  我们来打桌球吧
All right, let's play pool.
等下  老妈呢
Wait. Where's Mom?
-她和海伦在一起  -怎么会
- She went with Helen. - Why?
因为海伦想跟她谈谈  问问她
'Cause Helen wanted to talk to her and be, like,
"你为什么说我杀了我老公"
"Why do you think I killed my husband?"
她为什么会问那个
Why would she be like that?
因为我告诉她琳达认为她杀了她老公
'Cause I told her Linda thinks she killed her husband.
你为什么要告诉她
And why would you tell her that?!
因为我们是朋友  吉恩
Because we're friends, Gene!
天呐  我得赶紧去找她
Oh, my God. I got to find her!
好吧  海伦  你先别往前走了
Okay, Helen, just stop moving,
这样我也不用往后退了
and I'll stop moving.
小心点  琳达
Oh, Linda, be careful.
你刚好站在拉里掉下去的地方
You're standing almost exactly where Larry fell from.
那儿可滑了
It's very slippery.
退后  老姐  等等
Back off, sister! Wait.
你目睹拉里掉下去的时候在玫瑰园里  对吗
You were in the rose garden when you saw Larry fall, right?
是的  我绝对在玫瑰园里
I was. I was so in the rose garden.
那我从这儿怎么看不到玫瑰园
Then why can't we see the rose garden from this very spot?!
-可以啊  就在那儿  -哦  好吧
- You can. It's right there. - Oh, right, yeah.
-挺漂亮  -琳达  我没杀拉里  我爱拉里
- Pretty. - Linda, I didn't kill Larry. I loved Larry.
好吧  我不爱他  但我...挺喜欢他的
Okay, I didn't love him, but I... but I liked him.
-我喜欢当她妻子  -好好
- I liked being married to him. - Right, yeah, yeah.
好吧  我不喜欢当他妻子
Okay, I didn't like being married to him,
但我喜欢成为他妻子的那一刻
but I liked getting married to him.
-你说了算  -好吧我不喜欢我们的婚礼
- Yeah, sure. - Okay, I didn't like our wedding day.
那天可累死人了  但重点是  我没有杀人
It was a hard day. But the point is, I'm not a murderer.
-我没杀他  -好好好
- I didn't kill him. - Yeah, yeah, yeah.
好吧  我想过要杀他  谁不想呢
Okay, I thought about killing him. Who hasn't?
-但我没行动  我做不到  -好好
- But I didn't. I-I couldn't. -  Right, right.
-好吧  我做得到  但我没做  -好
- Okay, I could, but I didn't. - Oh, sure, yeah.
-因为他死了 -老天
- Because he died. - Oh, God!
-你救了我  -那是当然的啊
- You saved me. - Of course I did.
如果我让你掉下去  别人又会说是我杀了你
If I let you fall, they would think that I killed you,
我可不想再经历一次了
and I'm not going through that again.
谢谢你
Well, thank you.
抱歉说你是杀人犯了
I'm sorry for accusing you of murder.
你确定不是你干的吧
You definitely didn't do it?
绝对不是我干的
I definitely didn't do it.
不是你把他推下去的
You didn't push him and then kill him?
我谁也没推
I didn't push anybody!
好吧  来抱一个
All right. Well, give me huggies. Oh.
-我要把你推下去  -我的脸
- I'm pushing you! - Oh, my face!
开完笑的  我开  开玩笑的
No, I'm just kidding. I'm kid... I'm just kidding.
-放开我妈  -露易丝别  不是她干的
-Get away from my mom! - Louise, no! She didn't do it!
我的脖子
My neck!
太尖  太尖了
So sharp! Oh! So sharp!
-住手  住手  住手  -老天
- Stop! Stop! Stop! - Oh, boy!
-把她弄下来  -抱歉
- Get her off! - Sorry!
她不让我们给她剪指甲
She won't let us cut her nails.
太抱歉了  海伦  到底要我跟你们
I'm so sorry, Helen. How many times do I have
说多少次  海伦没有杀人
to tell you people? Helen is not a murderer!
我知道  我知道了  她跟我保证过了
I know, I know. She promised she didn't kill Larry.
现在我俩是朋友了
Now we're gal pals.
她当然没杀拉里
Of course she didn't kill Larry!
她是个好女人
She's a great woman.
她的锁骨还长得很有意思
And she's got interesting collar bones
额头也超美  而且  而且她
and a perfect forehead, and-and she's...
-我没想说那些话的  我...  -当心
- I didn't mean to say all that. I...  -  Look out!
那是客房卧室
That's the guest bedroom!
又一个卧室
Other bedroom!
我得把那屋顶板修一修
I got to fix that shingle!
大地  亲爱的大地
Ground. Sweet ground.
我还活着  各位
I'm alive, everyone!
-泰迪  -你掉得好远
- Teddy! - You fell so far!
-还掉了好久  -你居然还活着
- And for so long! - How are you alive?
我只是摔在平地上都走不动路了
I fell on the floor, and I can barely walk.
看来真的可以不小心滑下屋顶呢
I guess you can just slip and fall off the roof.
我天天摔下屋顶
I fall off roofs all the time.
海伦  你的说法过关了
Helen, your story checks out.
幸好你没事
I'm so glad you're okay.
-你刚在上面说的那些都是真的吗  -是吧
-Did-did you mean that stuff you said up there? - Uh, yeah?
我觉得你人也很好
Well, I think you're great
你的锁骨也很美
and have pretty good collarbones,
而且你要是把帽子摘下来
and if you ever took off that hat,
我敢说你的额头肯定能一直延伸到脑后
I bet you've got a forehead that goes all the way back.
真甜蜜
So sweet.
-我们进去吧  -好
- Let's get you inside. - Yeah.
看呐  这儿有个泥箱
Hey, look... A mud box.
亨利  我找到个东西
Hey, Henry, I found something.
-我看见了  -一个破工具箱
- I see you did. - Some crappy tool box.
我知道你为什么要把它埋起来
I know why you buried this.
是么
You do?
因为你不想让泰迪知道你有工具
Because you didn't want Teddy to think you had tools,
这样他才能来帮你修东西
so he'd come over and fix stuff.
没错
Right.
因为你喜欢他
Because you like him.
-是的  -没事儿
- I do. - It's okay.
我不会把你的秘密工具告诉别人的
I won't tell anybody about your secret tools.
反正我想你也不可能
You know, I don't think
记得今天发生的所有事
you're gonna remember any of this anyway.
-是啊  -我们进去吧
- Yeah. - Let's go inside.
我们难道不是在里面么
We're not inside?
听我说  亲爱的
So listen, honey,
下次你来我们镇上的话  你和
next time you're in town, you and,
泰迪一起来我们的餐馆吃饭  不要钱
Teddy come by, have dinner at the restaurant, on us.
-真的么  -那真是太好了
- What? - Well, I'd like that very much.
是什么样的餐馆
What kind of restaurant is it?
-徒有其表  -二流餐馆  -挺好的
- Slop shop. - Butt hut. - It's nice.
那说定了
I am in.
太好了  我现在就回去等着你
Perfect! I'll go there now and wait.
真是一次愉快的度假加冒险
What a wonderful little adventurecation!
我太难受了
Oh, I hurt so much.
回见  杀手
Take it easy, killer!
杀手
Killer.
好了  再见
Okay, see you soon!
-海伦  再给我一片药  -开车小心
- Helen, another pill. - Be safe!
-再给我一片  -给  再见
- Give me another pill. - Here you go. Buh-bye!
多谢
Thank you.
-别杀人哟  -没问题
- Don't kill anyone! - Nah, you got it!
真是个好姑娘
What a sweetheart.
我们下次去闯别人的湖边别墅吧
Ooh, let's go break into someone's lake house.
*我迷上了海伦*
*I'm falling for Helen*
*我不知道*
*And there's no tellin'*
*对像海伦这样穿衣棒*
*Just how far a fella can fall*
*体力好  大眼睛的寡妇我能爱到什么程度*
*For sure-fitted, strong-armed, wild-eyed widow like Helen *
*我不知道*
*And there's no tellin'*
*对像海伦这样*
*Just how far a fella can fall*
*嗑药  败家*
*For a pill-poppin', home-wreckin' *
*脖子长的寡妇我能爱到什么程度*
*Long-necked widow like Helen *
*我迷上了海伦*
*I'm falling for Helen... *